hanapinmarketing.com 2011-08-19

# Privacy Policy | Hanapin Marketing®

This website defines the ways in which Hanapin Marketing uses and protects the information that you provide when using our website. By using this website you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

We respect your privacy and are committed to ensuring that your personal information is protected. There are several circumstances on this website in which you may be asked to submit information from which you can be identified. Be assured that all information collected will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. 

Hanapin Marketing reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for updates and changes. This policy is effective April 16th, 2008. 

**Personal Information**  
There are several instances in which we may collect information from you. We may collect personally identifiable information that you provide such as name, phone number, and email address. Based on the information you provide, we may contact you (by phone or email) to respond to your inquiries or discuss our services. 

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. 

**Site Statistics Information**  
We also collect non-personal information from you such as browser type, URL of the previous website visited, ISP, operating system, and Internet protocol (IP) address. Non-personal information cannot be easily used to personally identify you. We use this information to analyze trends, administer the site, track users' movements around the site, and gather demographic information about our users. 

**Security**  
We are committed to ensuring the safety of your personal information. 

We follow accepted industry standards to protect the information you submit to us, both in transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of Internet transmission and electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your information, we cannot guarantee absolute security. 

If you believe any of the information we have about you is incomplete or incorrect, please contact us. We will promptly correct any inaccurate information. 

If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please contact [patrick.east@hanapimarketing.com](mailto:patrick.east@hanapimarketing.com), 525 S Walker St, Bloomington, IN 47403, 812.330.3134.
